RÉMY HANNEQUIN

Web developer

+33.6.78.40.18.50 hello@rhannequ.in

http://rhannequ.in

Paris, FR

30 years old



ABOUT

Web developer for more than 10 years, I am specialised in web projects development with Ruby and especially Ruby on Rails. I am currently Fullstack Engineer at Getaround.

I have been teaching Ruby and Rails in several schools and experienced freelancing outside my main activity.

SKILLS

Ruby / Rails

JavaScript

PostgreSQL / MySQL

Testing

CI / Tooling / Monitoring

English-speaking

HOBBIES

Handball

🍴 Cooking

Stargazing

Fermeting stuff

SOCIAL MEDIAS

github.com/rhannequin

in linkedin.com/rhannequin

twitter.com/rhannequin

EDUCATION

ESGI, 2014

Master degree in Web Engineering & E-business

IUT UPEM, 2013

Professional bachelor degree in Multimedia

IUT UPEM, 2011

Bachelor degree in Multimedia

EXPERIENCES

Getaround, since 2019 - Paris – Fullstack Engineer

In charge of developing new features, maintaining the current ones, monitoring and R&D in multiple squads of the product

RATP, 2014 to 2019 - *Paris* – Web projects manager and developer

Managing and developing with Ruby

Significant projects: Android app for maintainer, Ruby company apps generator, administration console

Web / Ruby Trainer, 2014 to 2019 - *Paris* – IUT UPEM & ESGI

Teaching Ruby, Rails, MVC pattern and building MVP

RATP, 2012 to 2014 - Paris – Web developer - Apprentice

Project management and development with Java, Ruby, JavaScript Significant projects: web app for monitoring IT department apps

Kontest, 2011 to 2012 - Paris - Web developer - Apprentice

Added features and games types (blindtest, video), used multiple API providers like Deezer, YouTube, Dailymotion. Added automated test suites.

Urbanmedia Ltd, 2011 - Singapore – Web developer - Intern

Added features for iOS and Android app and invoices generation